ERIK MORALES

TECHNICAL SUPPORT SPECIALIST

PROFILE

Professional Summary Tech guru, sales leader, customer service expert, problem solver, trend analyzer, and wearer of many hats. Ability to combine proven management, coaching, and technical solutions experience to create innovative solutions for clients while increasing revenue for the organization.

EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL SUCCESS MANAGER

Bazaarvoice | 2017 - Present

- Create web applications, develop technical solutions, troubleshoot hardware and software problems
- Identify trends, address client concerns, solve IT-related inquiries, handle code debugging
- Assess account information and analyze usage trends to better understand customers and grow sales
- Identify, build, and capitalize on new business opportunities, facilitate new feature adoption

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

2017

- Created customized web applications and oversaw deployment
- Applied technical expertise to assist clients with hardware and software issues and challenges
- Actively cultivated client relationships, built upon my technical skills and outstanding reliability

PROPERTY CLAIMS SPECIALIST

Liberty Mutual Insurance | 2015 -2016

- Worked directly with customers to assess damages, recommend repairs, and provide professional advice
- Used advanced software programs to design diagrams and present solutions
- Prepared comprehensive estimates, processed payments, and ensured overall client satisfaction

SOLUTIONS SPECIALIST

Verizon Wireless | 2011 -2015

- Selected to open and work at company's flagship store
- Recognized in 2012 Winner's Circle for achieving sales within top 10% for region
- Consistently exceeded sales goals by 20% on a monthly basis
- Trained, supervised and coached team members

MANAGER

AT&T | 2004 - 2011

- Regularly exceeded sales quotas for activations, features, accessories, and wired sales
- Maintained 90-100% customer service satisfaction level
- Chosen as one of 13 employees nationwide to help launch advanced training course
- Significantly contributed to the coordination and execution of outside sales events and promotional efforts
- Recruited, hired, and mentored staff for multiple locations
- More than doubled unit sales within two years

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Salesforce
- XN
- HTMI
- CSS
- JavaScript
- BootStrap
- jQuery
- FireBase
- React
- NodeJS
- DJango
- Python
- Mongoose
- Angular
- MongoDB
- postgresq

CONTACT

331.625.0923 morales.erik1@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/erik-morales github.com/emorale112

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Information Systems DePaul University